inonit.in 2018-04-08

# Privacy Policy Statement - Inonit.in

**Privacy Policy**

This document outlines the privacy policy of Inonit Internet Solutions Private Limited henceforth for the purpose of this document known as “Inonit” and the “you” the user of Inonit’s services henceforth referred to as the “Customer”. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit our website or register on it. Please read this notice carefully.

**Personal Information** Any information shared with us including your email address when you sign up for the newsletter, or phone number when you text-message a discount code or offer to yourself will never be sold, rented, or shared with any third parties for marketing purposes without your permission. We may share your personal information for the purpose of delivering e-mail to you or as required by law.

**Demographic Data** We may request you for other data like income, interests, gender etc. Though most of this information is optional, we may use it to improve our website and/or tailor your experience on our website, showing you content that we think you might be interested in and displaying content according to your preferences. We may share aggregated, anonymous information with advertisers interested in advertising on In On It via e-mail or on the site, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information like your e-mail, phone number, etc about you or any other person.

**Usage Information** In addition to collecting personal and non-personal information, Inonit may also collect non-personal, aggregated information about subscribers’ use of Inonit e-mails and the website. This information is not personally identifiable and will be used only to find out how subscribers use our service and site. For example, this information will tell us how much time users spend on the Inonit website, from which websites subscribers came, and to what sites subscribers go. The collection of this information allows us to, among other things, prepare for traffic load demands and be more efficient.

**Links to Other Sites** As part of the service, Inonit may create links allowing you to access third-party sites. Inonit is not responsible for the content that appears on these sites and does not endorse these sites. Please consult the sites’ individual privacy policies in order to determine how they treat user information.

**Security** All information described above is stored on restricted database servers.

**Modification to This Policy** Inonit reserves the right to change its policy at anytime in the future without prior notification.

**Contact Us** If you have any questions about this policy or our site in general, please contact us at support@inonit.in.
